A.M. Sullivan Papers
A. M. Sullivan Papers
- Correspondence - subject files
  - Hay, Sara Henderson, 1934; 1936,; 1939,; 1942-1955; includes introduction from radio broadcasts on Apr. 15, 1934 and May 24, 1936 (Box 4)
  - Hayden, (Mrs.) Charles, See McGinley, Phyllis
  - Healy, James A., 1952-1955 (Box 4)
  - Healy, Thomas, 1943 (Box 4)
  - Helton, Roy Addison, 1934; 1941; includes introduction from radio broadcast on May 6, 1934 (Box 4)
  - Henderson, Daniel Maclntyre, 1934; 1945 (Box 4)
  - Henrich, Edith, 1942 (Box 4)
  - Herndon, Brodie S., 1952; 1955 (Box 4)
  - Herron, Eileen Curran, See Curran, Eileen
  - Herron, Walter, See Curran, Eileen
  - Herzberg, Max J., 1955 (Box 4)
  - Hess, Mary Whitcomb, 1953-1954 (Box 4)
  - Heyden, Francis Joseph, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Hickey, Agnes MacCarthy, 1954; undated (Box 4)
  - Higgins, Frederick Robert, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 4)
  - Highet, Gilbert, 1957 (Box 4)
  - Hill, Frank Ernest, 1935; undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 5)
  - Hillyer, Robert S., 1947-1957; undated (Box 5)
  - Himmell, Sophie, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Hinkson, Pamela, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Hinton, Walter, 1929 (Box 5)
  - Hoagland, Clayton, 1955; undated (Box 5)
  - Hoeny, A. Winfield, undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 5)
  - Hoffman, Harold Giles, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Hogan, Patrick G., 1954-1955; 1961 (Box 5)
  - Holberg, Ruth Langland, 1933; 1944; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Aug. 6, 1933 (Box 5)
  - Holden, Raymond, 1936; includes interview from radio broadcast on May 24, 1936 (Box 5)
  - Holden, Sally, See Hay, Sara Henderson
  - Holland, Maurice, 1955-1956 (Box 5)
  - Holmes, John, 1951-1953; 1956 (Box 5)
  - Hospitalized Veterans Writing Project, 1954-1955 (Box 5)
  - Howard, Frances Minturn, 1946; 1950-1951,; 1957,; undated (Box 5)
  - Huberman, Edward, 1952 (Box 5)
  - Hughes, Dorothy Berry, See Columbia University
  - Hume, Paul, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Humphries, Rolfe, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 5)
  - Hunton, George K., 1950; 1955 (Box 5)
  - Hutchens, John K., 1947 (Box 5)
  - I, 1 folder (Box 5)
  - The Institute of Management Sciences (TIMS), 1961 (Box 5)
  - Irish Arts and Literary Society, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Irish Cultural Circle, Inc., 1954-1959 (Box 5)
  - Irish Digest, 1955 (Box 5)
  - "Irish Program(s)", 1933; undated; radio broadcast on Aug. 20, 1933 and undated broadcast (Box 5)
  - J, 1 folder (Box 5)
  - Jackson, Barbara Ward, 1956 (Box 5)
  - Jennings, Leslie Nelson, 1954; undated (Box 5)
  - Johns, Orrick, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 5)
  - Johnson, James Weldon, 1938; includes memorial radio broadcast for him on July 3, 1938 (Box 5)
  - Johnson, Norman, 1948; includes interview from radio broadcast on Aug. 20, 1948 (Box 5)
  - Jones, Robert Edmond, 1945? (Box 5)
  - Jones, Thomas S., dedication, radio broadcast; See Foley, John L.
  - K, 1 folder (Box 5)
  - Kahmann, Chesley, 1952-1953 (Box 5)
  - Kahn, Hannah, 1950-1952; 1956,; undated (Box 5)
  - Kane, Whitford, 1949; 1955 (Box 5)
  - Kantor, MacKinlay, 1934; includes interview from radio broadcast on Apr. 29, 1934 (Box 5)
  - Keith, Joseph Joel, 1953-1955 (Box 5)
  - Keller, Martha, 1948; 1951,; 1955,; undated (Box 5)
  - Kendall, Jeanine, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Kendall, Virginia, See The Catholic World
  - Kenedy (P. J.) & Sons, 1954-1958; undated (Box 5)
  - Kennedy, Eamon, 1947 (Box 5)
  - Kenny, Herbert A., 1956-1957 (Box 5)
  - Kenseth, Arnold, 1953 (Box 5)
  - Kenyon, Bernice, 1934; includes interview from radio broadcast on Feb. 25, 1934 (Box 5)
  - Kenyon, Theda, 1933; 1934,; undated; includes interview from radio broadcasts on Oct. 1, 1933, May 20, 1934, and undated broadcast (Box 5)
  - Keyhoe, Donald E., 1930 (Box 5)
  - Kieran, John, 1943 (Box 5)
  - Kilmer, Kenton, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 5)
  - King, Cameron, 1954; undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 5)
  - Kinkead, Eugene, 1954; 1957 (Box 5)
  - Kleiner, Rheinhart, 1924; 1925 (Box 5)
  - Kramer, Aaron, 1948; 1950,; 1957-1958; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Dec. 3, 1948 (Box 5)
  - Kreymborg, Alfred, 1942; 1948-1950 (Box 5)
  - Kruger, Fania, 1954-1955 (Box 5)
  - Kuhn, Irene Corbally, 1957 (Box 5)
  - L, 1 folder (Box 5)
  - La Farge, Christopher, 1939; 1940,; 1947,; 1950; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Apr. 15, 1939 (Box 5)
  - Laidlaw, Louise Burton, undated; includes interview from radio broadcast on Apr. 25, ? (Box 5)
  - Laing, Alexander, 1934; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Feb. 4, 1934 (Box 5)
  - Landreth, Helen, 1936; includes interview from radio broadcast on Nov. 1, 1936 (Box 6)
  - Laramore, Vivian Yeiser, 1925 (Box 6)
  - Lawrence, Gordon, 1925; 1933; includes introduction from radio broadcast on June 25, 1933 (Box 6)
  - Leach, Henry Goddard, 1954-1958 (Box 6)
  - Leach, Leacy Naylor Green, 1925 (Box 6)
  - League of American Writers Program, undated; radio broadcast (Box 6)
  - Leamy, Edmund, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 6)
  - Leamy, Margaret, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 6)
  - Lebhar, Godfrey Montague, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Lee, Alfred McClung, 1955 (Box 6)
  - Lee, Lawrence, 1948; includes interview from radio broadcast on Oct. 22, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Lee, Muna, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Lehigh University, 1961; undated (Box 6)
  - Leitch, Mary Sinton, 1953 (Box 6)
  - Lieberman, Elias, 1933; 1948,; 1951; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Oct. 8, 1933 (Box 6)
  - Lissner., Will, 1956; 1966 (Box 6)
  - Litsey, Sarah, See Hasselriis, Caspar Henrik Wolffsen
  - Livermore, Shaw, 1957 (Box 6)
  - Logan, Douglas, 1953-1954 (Box 6)
  - Lopatnikov, Nikolai (Mrs.), See Hay, Sara Henderson
  - Loving, Pierre, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 6)
  - Luce, Clare Booth, 1956 (Box 6)
  - Luckner, Felix, 1929 (Box 6)
  - Lundbergh, Holger, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 6)
  - Lynch, Frank Curtis, 1964; 1965 (Box 6)
  - Ma-Me, 1 folder (Box 6)
  - Mf-Mz, 1 folder (Box 6)
  - Maas, Willard, undated (Box 6)
  - McBride, Mary Margaret, 1941-1942; 1950-1951 (Box 6)
  - McBrown, Gertrude Parthenia, 1957 (Box 6)
  - McConnell, Albert Joseph, 1955 (Box 6)
  - McCord, David, 1934; includes interview from radio broadcast on Apr. 8, 1934 (Box 6)
  - McCormick, Richard Patrick, 1952 (Box 6)
  - McDaniel, Weston Owen, 1952 (Box 6)
  - McDonnell, Thomas P., 1957 (Box 6)
  - McGinley, Phyllis, 1952-1955; 1966 (Box 6)
  - McGinnis, Patrick B., 1958 (Box 6)
  - McGuinness, Charles John, 1947; undated (Box 6)
  - McGurrin, James, 1954; 1955 (Box 6)
  - McHenry, Roy C., 1947-1948 (Box 6)
  - MacKaye, Percy, 1948-1950; 1954-1957 (Box 6)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1940-1941; undated (Box 6)
  - MacManus, Seumas, 1955-1956; undated (Box 6)
  - Declan X. McMullen Company, 1948; 1955,; undated (Box 6)
  - MacNeil, Neil, 1948 (Box 6)
  - Maher, James, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Mahoney, Tom, 1957 (Box 6)
  - Mansfield, Beatrice Cameron, 1940 (Box 6)
  - Mansfield, Richard, 1950-1952 (Box 6)
  - Manville, Herbert Emery, 1925 (Box 6)
  - Markham, Anna Catherine, 1933-1934; undated; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Dec. 31, 1933 (Box 6)
  - Markham, Edwin, 1933; 1934,; 1948-1954,; 1940,; undated; includes introduction from radio broadcasts on Mar. 12, 1933 and Apr. 27, 1934; 2 folders (Box 6)
  - Markham, Edwin, printed material (Box 6)
  - Markham, Virgil, 1934-1935; 1958-1959 (Box 6)
  - Marquand, John P., 1941 (Box 6)
  - Sister Mary Madeleva, 1954-1956 (Box 7)
  - Masefield, John, 1950; 1951 (Box 7)
  - Mason, Madeline, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Masters, Edgar Lee
    - 1936, 1940-1945, 2 folders; includes introduction from radio broadcasts on July 26, 1936 and Sept. 27, 1936 (Box 7)
    - Correspondence about, 1940-1944; 1949-1950 (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Clippings (Box 7)
    - Printed material (Box 7)
    - Writings (Box 7)
  - Masters, Ellen (Mrs. Edgar Lee), 1951 (Box 7)
  - Masters, Marcia, 1952; undated (Box 7)
  - Mattice, Paul B., 1947; 1948 (Box 7)
  - Maxwell, Gilbert, undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 7)
  - Meacham, Harry M., 1955-1956; 1959 (Box 7)
  - Medina, Harold R., 1950 (Box 7)
  - "Memorial [Day] Programs", 1934; 1936,; undated; radio broadcasts on May 31, 1934, May 31, 1936 and undated broadcast (Box 7)
  - "Memorial Program for Harriet Monroe", radio broadcast; See Monroe, Harriet
  - Miller, Spencer, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Monroe, Harriet, 1933; 1936; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Jan. 29, 1933 and memorial broadcast on Nov. 17, 1936 (Box 7)
  - Montgomery, Roselle Mercier, 1925 (Box 7)
  - Mooney, Ria, 1954; 1956 (Box 7)
  - Moore, Douglas Stuart, undated (Box 7)
  - Moore, Marianne, 1941-1944; 1950,; 1954-1956 (Box 7)
  - Moore, Merrill, 1952; undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 7)
  - Moore, Robert Thomas, 1954-1957 (Box 7)
  - Morgan, Angela, 1950 (Box 7)
  - Moriarty, Francis Edwin, See St. Michael's College
  - Morton, David, 1933; 1938,; 1949,; undated; includes introduction from radio broadcast on June 11, 1933 and undated broadcast (Box 7)
  - Moskowitz, Henry, 1925 (Box 7)
  - Movietone News, 1951; 1955,; 1957 (Box 7)
  - Moyne, Bryan Walter Guinness, See Guinness, Bryan Walter
  - Mullins, Helene, See Roberts, Walter Adolphe
  - Munson, Gorham, 1948; 1956; includes introduction from radio broadcast on July 23, 1948 (Box 7)
  - Murphy, John Maher, 1944; undated (Box 7)
  - Murray, T. C., 1950; 1951 (Box 7)
  - Myers, Betty, 1934; includes interview from radio broadcast on June 3, 1934 (Box 7)
  - Myers, Robert Manson, 1955 (Box 7)
  - N, 1 folder (Box 7)
  - Nardi, Marcia, 1950; undated (Box 7)
  - Narveson, Robert, 1957 (Box 7)
  - Nathan, Robert, 1941; undated (Box 7)
  - National Broadcasting Company 1959 (Box 7)
  - National League of American Penwomen, See Benton, Patricia
  - National Office Furniture Association, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 7)
  - Native American literature, undated; undated radio broadcast (Box 7)
  - Natural History Magazine, 1953 (Box 7)
  - "Negro Poetry", radio broadcast; See Johnson, Norman
  - Neihardt, John Gneisenau, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Neilson, Francis, 1955-1958 (Box 7)
  - "The New Poetry", 1934; 1957,; undated; radio broadcast (Box 7)
  - Newman, I. H., 1925; undated (Box 7)
  - Newman, J. Wilson, 1954-1958 (Box 7)
  - Nicholl, Louise Townsend, 1948-1957 (Box 7)
  - Noyes, Alfred, 1944 (Box 7)
  - O, 1 folder (Box 7)
  - O'Brien, Katharine, 1955 (Box 7)
  - O'Brien, Michael Joseph, 1948 (Box 7)
  - O'Brien, Sean, 1940-1943; undated (Box 7)
  - O'Brien, Seumas, 1934; 1938-1957,; undated; includes introduction from radio broadcast on May 13, 1934; 4 folders (Box 8)
  - O'Connell, Robert J., 1956 (Box 8)
  - O'Conor, Norreys Jephson, 1954-1955 (Box 8)
  - O'Farachian, Roibeard, See Farren, Robert
  - O'Flaherty, Liam, undated (Box 8)
  - O'Ryan, John F., 1930 (Box 8)
  - O'Sheel, Shaemas (and Annette), 1938-1957; undated (Box 8)
  - O'Sullivan, Seumas, 1953-1955 (Box 8)
  - P, 1 folder (Box 8)
  - Patterson, Elizabeth B., 1954-1956 (Box 8)
  - Pauker, Edmond, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Pegler, Westbrook, 1940-1941 (Box 8)
  - Peloubet, Maurice E., 1951-1957; See also The Poetry Society of America (Box 8)
  - Personnel Management for Executives Conference, 1959; 1960 (Box 8)
  - Pick, John, 1944 (Box 8)
  - Piercy, Josephine Ketcham, 1955 (Box 8)
  - Pim, Sheila, 1953-1956 (Box 8)
  - Poetry: a Magazine of Verse, 1938; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Feb. 13, 1938 (Box 8)
  - Poetry Awards, See Moore, Robert Thomas
  - The Poetry Society of America, 1941-1942; 1949-1958,; 1965,; undated; See also Peloubet, Maurice (Box 8)
  - Pollock, Channing, 1931 (Box 8)
  - Pratt, Edwin J. (Ned), 1948-1951; undated (Box 8)
  - Price, William James, 1925 (Box 8)
  - Pulsifer, Harold Trowbridge, 1938 (Box 8)
  - Putnam, George Palmer, 1930 (Box 8)
  - Q, 1 folder (Box 8)
  - Quinn, Arthur Hobson, 1942 (Box 8)
  - R, 1 folder (Box 8)
  - Raftery, Gerald, 1934; undated; includes interview from radio broadcast on Mar. 18, 1934 and undated broadcast (Box 8)
  - Raley, Loker, 1940 (Box 8)
  - Reardon, Mark S., 1955 (Box 8)
  - Redmond, Liam, undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcasts (Box 8)
  - Reilly, Joseph, 1952-1956 (Box 8)
  - Richards, Rosa Coates, 1954-1955 (Box 8)
  - Richardson, Stanley, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 8)
  - Riemer, George R., 1954 (Box 8)
  - Ritter, Margaret Tod, 1941 (Box 8)
  - Robb, Wallace Havelock, 1937 (Box 8)
  - Roberts, Ruby Altizer, 1950; 1956 (Box 8)
  - Roberts, Walter Adolphe, 1933; 1941,; undated; includes introduction from radio broadcast Apr. 16, 1933 and undated broadcast (Box 8)
  - "Edwin Arlington Robinson Program", radio broadcast; See Kenyon, Theda
  - Robinson, Henry Morton, 1937?; 1951,; 1954; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Jan. 16, 1937? (Box 9)
  - Robinson, Lennox, undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Rodman, Selden, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Romatka, Anton, 1925 (Box 9)
  - Ronalds, Francis Spring, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1948 (Box 9)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1937; 1938,; 1940; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Jan. 30, 1937 (Box 9)
  - Rorty, James, 1934; includes interview from radio broadcast on June 24, 1934 (Box 9)
  - Ross, Patrick Hore Warriner, 1925 (Box 9)
  - Rotary Club of New York, 1955; 1957 (Box 9)
  - Rowland, Martha Keller, See Keller, Martha
  - Rubin, Vera, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Russell, George, See "A. E. Memorial Program"
  - Russell, Sydney King, 1955; 1956,; undated (Box 9)
  - Ryan, Alvan Sherman, 1954; 1955 (Box 9)
  - S, 1 folder (Box 9)
  - "St. Francis Program", undated; radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - St. Michael's College, 1954-1955 (Box 9)
  - St. Patrick programs, 1934; 1954; radio broadcasts on Mar. 17, 1934 and Mar. 14, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Salomon, Isidore Lawrence, 1957 (Box 9)
  - Sampley, Arthur McCullough, 1953; 1955 (Box 9)
  - Sangster, Margaret Elizabeth, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Sarett, Lew, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
  - Sarton, May, 1953 (Box 9)
  - The Saturday Review, 1947-1957; See also Benet, William Rose (Box 9)
  - Saunders, Louise, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Seaman's Church Institute of New York, 1954-1957 (Box 9)
  - Sergeant, Howard, 1954 (Box 9)
  - Seward, William W., 1954; 1963 (Box 9)
  - Sheerin, John B., See The Catholic World
  - Shepperd, Tad, undated; includes interview from radio broadcast on Dec. 18, ? (Box 9)
  - Simpson, Maxwell Stewart, 1947 (Box 9)
  - "69th Regiment Program", 1934; 1938,; undated; radio broadcast on July 15, 1934 (Box 9)
  - Skinner, Cornelia Otis, 1957 (Box 9)
  - Sloane, Thomas O., 1948; 1955 (Box 9)
  - Smith, Chard Powers, 1934; undated; includes interview from radio broadcast on Feb. 18, 1934 and undated broadcast (Box 9)
  - Society for the Advancement of Management (Mohawk Valley Chapter), 1959 (Box 9)
  - "Soldier Poets", undated; radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Solum, Sjanna, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Southern Humanities Conference, See Hogan, Patrick G.
  - Speyer, Leonora, 1948-1952; undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Spire, Andre, 1942 (Box 9)
  - Spirit, See Brunini, John Gilland
  - Stearns, Florence Dickinson, 1954-1957 (Box 9)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Steinman, D. B., 1955 (Box 9)
  - Stevens, Wallace, 1950-1951 (Box 9)
  - Stickney, Helen Frith, 1956 (Box 9)
  - Stork, Charles Wharton, undated (Box 9)
  - Stringer, Arthur John, 1948; 1950 (Box 9)
  - Stuart, Jesse, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Sullivan, A. M., undated; poetry reading and radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Sullivan, Louis, printed material (Box 9)
  - Sullivan Shrine, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Sweeney, John L., 1957 (Box 9)
  - Swinburne, Algernon Charles, memorial and radio broadcast; See Roberts, Walter Adolphe
  - T, 1 folder (Box 9)
  - Taggard, Genevieve, undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Tate, Allen, 1941 (Box 9)
  - Taylor, Henry W., 1938; includes interview from radio broadcast on Feb. 27, 1938 (Box 9)
  - Teasdale, Sara, 1938; includes dedication from radio broadcast on Feb. 20, 1938 (Box 9)
  - Thaden, Louise, 1930 (Box 9)
  - Tichenor, Frank A., 1929 (Box 9)
  - Tobin, James Edward 1954 (Box 9)
  - Tolbert, Frank X., 1955 (Box 9)
  - Torrence, Ridgely, 1933; 1938-1948; includes introduction from radio broadcast on July 39, 1933 (Box 9)
  - Towne, Charles Hanson, 1945; undated (Box 9)
  - Tusiani, Joseph, 1957 (Box 9)
  - U, 1 folder (Box 9)
  - Untermeyer, Jean Starr, 1940; undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 9)
  - Untermeyer, Louis, 1939 (Box 9)
  - V, 1 folder (Box 9)
  - Valle, Isabel, 1938 (Box 9)
  - Van Doren, Carl, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Van Doren, Mark, 1940; 1941,; 1948-1958,; undated (Box 9)
  - Van Engen, Henry, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Van Vechten, Carl, 1926 (Box 10)
  - Verhesen, Fernand, undated (Box 10)
  - Viereck, Peter, 1949-1952 (Box 10)
  - Vilas, Faith, 1933; 1948; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Sept. 10, 1933 (Box 10)
  - Vinal, Harold, 1934; 1933,; 1948,; 1954-1957; includes introduction from radio broadcasts on May 28, 1933, Feb 18, 1934, and Oct. 8, 1948 (Box 10)
  - The Virginia Quarterly Review, 1955 (Box 10)
  - Vroman, Myron, 1953; 1956,; 1957; See also Writings: Poetry: "Tim Murphy, Morgan Rifleman:" research material (Box 10)
  - W, 1 folder (Box 10)
  - Wagstaff, Blanche Shoemaker, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 10)
  - Walsh, Joseph Cyrillus, 1954; undated (Box 10)
  - Walsh, Lorna Gill, 1941-1943 (Box 10)
  - Wang, Yang, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Ward, Barbara, See Jackson, Barbara Ward
  - Ward Manor, 1948-1949 (Box 10)
  - Ward, May Williams, 1949; 1951 (Box 10)
  - Warren, Elinor Remick, 1954 (Box 10)
  - Weaver, John V. A., undated; includes tribute from undated radio broadcast (Box 10)
  - Welles, Winifred, undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 10)
  - Wells, Henry Willis, 1942; 1944 (Box 10)
  - Wenham, Edward, 1949-1956 (Box 10)
  - Wheelock, John Hall, 1938; 1950,; 1956,; 1966,; undated; includes introduction from radio broadcasts on Feb. 20, 1938, May 9, ?, and undated broadcast (Box 10)
  - Whitefield, Grace Woodley, 1954 (Box 10)
  - Whitney, Barbara, 1955; correspondence about (Box 10)
  - Whyte, William Hamilton, 1957 (Box 10)
  - Widdemer, Margaret, 1933; 1941,; 1942,; 1947-1957,; undated; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Apr. 20, 1933 and undated broadcast (Box 10)
  - Wilder, Charlotte, See Daly, James
  - Williams, William Carlos, undated; includes interview from undated radio broadcast (Box 10)
  - Willis, William, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Wood, Clement, 1950 (Box 10)
  - Woodall, Allen E., undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast and scripts (Box 10)
  - Wrinn, Mary J. J., 1939?; 1955-1957; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Apr. 22, 1939? (Box 10)
  - Wurdemann, Audrey, 1934; undated; includes interview from radio broadcasts on Feb. 11, 1934, Mar. 4, 1934, and Nov. 29, ? (Box 10)
  - Y, 1 folder (Box 10)
  - Yancey, Lewis Alonso, 1930; 1932 (Box 10)
  - Yeats, William Butler, 1933 (Box 10)
  - Young, Barbara, 1934; undated; includes introduction from radio broadcast on Jan. 14, 1934 (Box 10)
  - Young American poets, undated; radio broadcasts (Box 10)
  - Yurka, Blanche, 1954 (Box 10)
  - Zaturenska, Marya, undated; includes introduction from undated radio broadcast (Box 10)
  - Zoll, Howard S., 1955; 1956 (Box 10)
- Writings
  - Books
    - Ballad of a Man Named Smith, draft (Box 11)
    - The Ballad of John Castner
      - Research material (Box 11)
      - Draft (Box 11)
    - The Bottom of the Sea
      - Research material, 5 folders (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, 1945-1967 (Box 11)
      - Proposal to publish (Box 11)
      - Arrangement (Box 11)
      - Front matter (Box 11)
      - Publication references and credits (Box 11)
      - Poems (by title), drafts, revisions; 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Additions, revisions, 2 folders (Box 11)
      - Side panels (Box 11)
      - P. 1-33, 2 folders (Box 12)
      - "Nicholls key set of text" p. 1-33 (Box 12)
      - "Williamson proofs" p. 1-33 (Box 12)
      - Drafts p. 1-40 (various paging), 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Typescript drafts, 9 folders (Box 12)
      - Typescript manuscript, 13 folders (Box 13)
      - Production records, 11 folders (Box 14)
      - Production records, 8 folders (Box 15)
      - Miscellany (Box 15)
    - A Day in Manhattan, typescript manuscript; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - "Harvey Merrill"
      - "Unpublished and not to be published", typescript manuscript (Box 16)
      - Typescript manuscript with illustrations, 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Incident in Silver, typescript manuscript (Box 16)
    - New Jersey Hills, preface, epilogue (Box 16)
    - "Notes on a Sentimental Journey", unpublished, typescript manuscript; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Psalms of the Prodigal, and Other Poems, typescript manuscript (Box 16)
    - The Return and Other Irish Poems, typescript manuscript (Box 16)
    - Stars and Atoms Have No Size, typescript manuscript (Box 16)
    - "There is No Prose", book outline (Box 16)
    - The Three-Dimensional Man, typescript manuscript; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Tim Murphy, Morgan Rifleman, and Other Ballads, publicity (Box 16)
  - Essays
    - Business (by title)
      - A-P, 12 folders (Box 17)
      - R-Z and untitled, 9 folders (Box 18)
    - Literary (by title)
      - A-Fr, 5 folders (Box 18)
      - Fs-T, 14 folders (Box 19)
      - U-Z and untitled, 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous (by title), 4 folders (Box 20)
  - Poetry
    - "Footnote to Tragedy", typescript (Box 20)
    - "In the Beginning Was the Word", typescript (Box 20)
    - "Inauguration Poem", typescript (Box 20)
    - "Tim Murphy, Morgan Rifleman"
      - Research material, 6 folders; See also Vroman, Myron (Box 20)
      - Holograph drafts (Box 20)
      - Introduction, typescript drafts with holograph corrections (Box 20)
      - Incidents A-0, drafts; 4 folders (Box 21)
    - "Transcontinental", typescript manuscript (Box 21)
  - Reviews
    - By title, 4 folders (Box 21)
  - Scripts
    - "The Ballad of John Castner", typescript manuscript (Box 21)
    - "The Bird With the Feathery Face", typescript manuscript (Box 21)
    - "A Day in Manhattan," Columbia Workshop, typescript manuscript (Box 21)
    - "A Matter of Conscience", typescript manuscript with holograph corrections (Box 21)
    - "Wings for an Eagle," Columbia Workshop, typescript manuscript (Box 21)
  - Speeches
    - Literary (by title) (Box 21)
  - Stories
    - "Blind Man's Bluff", typescript manuscript (Box 21)
    - "Every Country House a Zoo", typescript manuscript with holograph corrections (Box 21)
  - Miscellany
    - Discoveries and Inventions, by Percy MacKaye, typescript draft of Foreword by A.M. Sullivan (Box 21)
    - Poems, by Francis Neilson, typescript draft of foreword by A. M. Sullivan (Box 21)
    - Travel reminiscence (untitled), Southern United States tour (Box 21)
    - Gaelic script, unidentified (Box 21)
  - Published material
    - Articles
      - Business (by title)
        - A-H, 2 folders (Box 21)
        - I-Z (Box 22)
      - Literary, 1951; 1953,; undated (Box 22)
    - Books
      - The Ballad of Dick Dowling, American Irish Historical Society, c1954 (Box 22)
      - Elbows in the Wind, published excerpts (Box 22)